Guide to the Robert Schediwy Papers, 1970-1998
Department of Special Collections
Robert Schediwy Papers,
1970-1998
Special Collections M0762
Schediwy, Robert.
9.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection closed until 2050, except with permission of author and library.
Provenance
Gift of Robert Schediwy, 1995, 1996, 1997, and 1998.
Scope and Content
Diaries, typescripts, publications (photocopies; originals with donor)
Access Terms
Austria--Social history.
Container List
- Diaries 1 [1988], (Photocopies). (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Diaries 2A [1988], (Photocopies). (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Diaries 2B [1988], (Photocopies). (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Diaries 3 [1988], (Photocopies). (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Newspaper articles on urban architecture [1992-95], (Photocopies) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Wiener Zeitung; "Ein Dschungel namens Tokyo" by Schediwy. [Feb. 2, 1993] (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photocopies of articles on Keynes, Austrian economy, psychoanalysis and Dr. Seuss [1984-1994] (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Photocopies of articles in "Gegenwart" (Art and Dictatorship; Architecture). [1993-1994] (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "Gegenwart" (Journal, articles on Keynes and Canetti) [ Oct.-Dec. 1994] (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Diaries [Feb. 1994], (typescript). (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Typescript of an two-part interview with Bruno Kreisky [1985/86]. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Review on architecture [1993] (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Printed articles on literature, economy and psychoanalysis. [1983-91] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Collection of articles on architecture: "Wiener Metropolenträume 1988-1993"; typescripts. [1988-93] (Box 3, Folder 4)
- "Wiener Kunsthefte" (Journal). [Dec. 1994] (Box 3, Folder 5)
- "Die Zukunft" [May 1995], (Journal). (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Epiloque for: "From Failed Communism to Underdeveloped Capitalism" (Adam Zwass). (Photocopies) [1995] (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Diaries, #4-12, 1970-1987, (photocopies) (Box 4 (print box))
- Diaries, 1989, (photocopies) (Box 4 (print box))
  95-180, 2 linear ft.
- Diary, 1990., Photocopy (Box 5 (print box))
  96-022
- Diary, 1993-1994., Typescript (Box 6)
- Diary, 1995 (Jan-Dec); and 1996 (Jan-Apr) (Box 7)
  96-158, .5 linear ft.
- Diary, 1991., Photocopy (Box 8 (print box))
  96-179